kwconnect.com 2017-06-06

# Welcome to KWConnect!

Keller Williams Realty, Inc. ("KWRI") has developed a password-protected, secure intranet training Website (the "Intranet") that allows our franchisees and their independent contractors ("Associates") and employees to view, download and print all or portions of confidential documents and materials, to download approved advertising materials, to communicate with us and others, and to perform other functions that pertain to the operations of our franchisees, Associates and their businesses. Below is the Privacy Policy which informs you of our collection and usage policies and practices that apply to information collected through KWRI's Intranet. Please read and review the Privacy Policy carefully. By using and accessing the Intranet, you expressly acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE INTRANET. KWRI reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time. Such modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting. By using the Intranet after we have posted the modifications, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

## Collection of Information

When you visit the Intranet, KWRI collects information about you and your browsing habits. The information we collect depends on the pages you visit and what you do during your time using the Intranet.

We will record your user ID and password when we issue it to you. We also record each instance that your user ID and password are used to access the Intranet. We may also record time, duration and other details of your Intranet sessions. In addition, your first and last name will be transmitted with each message sent under your user ID.

KWRI may collect information from you automatically when you visit our Intranet, which may include the name of the domain and host from which you access the Intranet, the Internet protocol ("IP") address of your computer, the type of browser and software operating system you use, the date and time you access our Website, and the Internet address of the Website from which you linked to our site. KWRI may collect IP addresses and other publicly available data associated with a Web resource request. When users request pages from KWRI sites, our servers log the data the users' browser freely sends to our servers and the associated log-in data. We will use IP addresses, log-in information and other information provided by the users' Web browser to identify a user when we feel it is necessary.

KWRI may use cookies to enhance browsing on our Intranet. Cookies are small files or records that are placed on your computer's hard drive to collect information about your activities on our Website. You can choose to have your browser warn you every time a cookie is being sent to you and you can turn off cookie placement. If you refuse, your overall Intranet experience can be affected and you may be prevented from fully using and accessing the Intranet. KWRI may also use "message format" and "message open" sensing technologies to enable KWRI to recognize whether you have enabled your email program to receive HTML emails. If so, this information is associated with your email address so that we can send subsequent messages to you in HTML format. The "message open" sensing technology allows us to recognize whether you have opened our email messages. We can only detect this if you have enabled your email program to receive HTML emails.

## Use of Information

KWRI uses the information it collects (whether submitted by you or automatically collected) to respond to your requests, to provide you with information that KWRI thinks may be of interest to you and to operate its business. KWRI may also disclose your information to its affiliates, franchisees, Associates or other third parties. In addition, KWRI may disclose aggregated data and statistics to describe the Intranet to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. KWRI may disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be in violation of the Terms of Use or Privacy Policy or may be causing injury to or interference with any KWRI rights or property, other KWRI users or anyone else. KWRI may disclose or access account information when we believe the law requires it and for administrative or other purposes that we deem necessary.

## Underage Users

KWRI's Intranet was not designed nor intended to collect information from children under the age of 13. KWRI does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If you are younger than age 18, you should not use or have access to our Intranet.

## Links to Third-Party Sites

When you click on links that take you to third-party Websites, you will be subject to the third party's privacy policies. KWRI is not responsible for the contents or actions of any third-party Websites. The inclusion of a link to third-party Websites on KWRI's Intranet does not imply an endorsement of the site or of the provider of the site. We encourage you to read the posted Privacy Policy and Terms of Use of every site you visit.

## Questions or Comments

If you have any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact Keller Williams Realty, Inc., Attn: Legal Department, at 1221 S. MoPac Expwy, Ste. 400, Austin, Texas 78746 or to [legal@kw.com](mailto:legal@kw.com).
